Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
Grr, come on!
Oh, come on!
-Come on, start!
-Start!
-Come on, ya heap o' junk!
-Come on!
Heap o' junk!
-Whoosh!
-There it goes!
This episode of Bluey
is called BBQ.
-Okay.
You've got to.
And they're blowing the whistle,
the farmer's yelling,
"It's dog versus sheep!"
Oh, wow!
Don't you hate that dog shampoo?
But it does get the ticks.
There. Table's set.
Almost ready with the sausages, kids!
I love sausages!
Ruff, ruff, rowwrrr!
This is my relaxer chair.
It's where I relax.
Ahh! So relaxing.
Tell me about it.
Bandit had one on the back
of his ear the other day.
He kept going, "Ooh! Ooh!"
We have to have salad with our barbecue!
You're right, Muffin!
Bingo, can you be in charge of the salads?
Well, I was relaxing
in my relaxing chair, but okay.
Ooh, that sun is hot.
-Can I borrow this, Dad?
-Hey!
Okay, this is the salad bowl.
Ahhhh!
You need to put salad in it!
R-R-R-Rowwrrr!
I like pepper salad!
Ooh, me too. I love peppers.
Rowrr, rowrr! Gleen pepper!
Socks said she likes
green peppers the best.
Ooh! Oh, okay.
I can get green pepper.
Green is easy.
-Aah! Thorns!
Oh, here we go.
-Eeeeeeeeeeeee...
-Eee, bug!
-...eee!
-He was going-- Yaah!
-Get it off!
Oh, this one's okay.
There. Green pepper salad.
Ahh. So relaxing.
Can I have some yellow pepper?
Yellow's my favorite color pepper.
Hmm, yellow pepper.
Eh!
Unh!
Almost.
He doesn't listen to the farmer.
He goes straight for the sheep.
-Oh, no way!
-Just borrowing this, Dad!
Gets five of them. They're up over.
They're in the truck.
-Hey!
Unh, it's so heavy!
There!
-That's not safe, Bingo.
-Aah, aah, Mum!
Hmm.
Ooh!
Unh!
And then --hey!
Bingo!
Got it!
Sorry, Dad!
Here you go-- yellow pepper.
Ruff! Rowrr!
Now I'm gonna relax.
Ahhh!
My favorite color pepper is red pepper.
Red pepper?
There's no red plants
around, though, Muffin.
Yes, there is-- in that tree.
Oh, yeah! The Poinciana.
Aah! Aah!
Aaaah!
Red pepper!
I mean-- Oh!
Bingo, what are you doing?
I'm making a salad!
Okay!
Yaah!
Yeah!
There!
-Red pepper.
-Yeah!
I don't think there's
any more colors of pepper.
So now... I'm only...
I'm just gonna...
relax in my... relaxer chair.
Ooh, I like that salad dressing, Chilli.
Yeah, thanks. I made it myself.
It's Aunty Mary's recipe.
We need salad dressing!
Oooowwrrr!
Ahhh, okay.
-So, what'd you do?
-Well --
Can I borrow this, Dad?
-Hey!
Mud. All mine.
Oh, we're out of mud.
I will make some more.
Dad, which way do I turn on the hose?!
Urghh! Dad!
Yes, Bingo!
-Oh!
Don't worry! I got it working!
There. Now I'll fill up my jar.
I'll just put this down here.
-It's raining.
Bingo, what are you doing down there?!
Bingo, grab the hose!
I'm trying! Aaaah!
It's tickling my bottom!
-Forget the hose!
Turn off the tap!
- No, no, no!
The other way. Right to tight!
Got it!
- Yeah!
- Awoooo!
My goodness!
This is not relaxing.
Salad dressing!
Now, I'm going to sit
in my relaxer chair and relax!
Hmph!
Whose muddy footprints are these?!
More sausages, please, Bluey.
Here ya go.
Thank you.
Phew! Finally, I get to relax!
Ahhhh!
Sausages are ready!
- Sausages!
- Awooo!
Ohhh!
Out of the way, salads.
-Ohh, looks good, Bandit!
-Ooh!
Well done. They look delicious, Bandit.
Why, thank you. Thank you very much.
Isn't anyone going to mention the salads?!
Check it out, kids.
Look how good they look.
-Thank you.
Thanks, Bingo. Now relax.
Yum, yum, yum!