Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
Ooh!
Morning, balloons!
I mean, morning, last balloon.
You ready?
Ready!
Keep your arms up!
-Aah!
- Again!
Morning, Bluey!
Oh, what have you got there?
This is my pet bird.
She's saying good morniiiing!
Oh, good morning, pet birdie.
Go free, birdie!
Oh, that's funny, is it?
-Yeah!
-Yeah, it is.
Well, I've got a game for you.
Is it keepy uppy?
Yeah, it's keepy uppy.
It's keepy uppy! Whoo!
This episode of Bluey
is called Keepy Uppy.
What's keepy uppy?
You have to keep
the balloon in the air
and can't let it
touch the ground.
What happens
if it touches the ground?
Oh, nothing Bingo.
It's just a game.
Oh, okay.
You ready?
-Yeah!
Okay... go!
Yeah. Bwut!
Bwut!
Ah, Bingo, quick!
Yah!
Bwut!
I got it, Bluey!
Bwut! You, get it!
-I got it. I got it.
-Bluey, get it!
Whoo!
-I got it!
-Oh, good.
No no no, quick! Quick!
-Bwut!
-Ah, Mum, you're making it harder!
Okay, I'm gonna
cook brecky, kids.
-Bwut!
-Mum!
Look, what if we do small ones?
Bwut!
Bwut! This is so easy now.
-Check it out, Mum!
-Bwut!
Bwut!
Hey, nice strategy,
balloon girls!
I'm a keepy uppy expert.
Yep. But it's not as fun now.
Can you make it hard again?
Sorry, pickle,
I've got my hands full.
Oh, good morning, everybody!
Said good morning, everyone!
Ugh! Whaddup, party people?
Dad, we're playing keepy uppy.
Can you make it harder?
Ah! My newspaper.
-Dad!
-Aah! Bingo, help!
I can't! I'm a newspaper!
-Oh, old so and so is at it again.
-Er, yes, yes.
Look! Wow.
Whoa. Look at that!
Bluey, help!
I'll save ya, Bingo!
Let her go.
Oh, you want to read
the newspaper, Bluey?
Okay, just don't do the sudoku.
Oh, look. Lovely orange juice.
Yes, please!
-Aah!
No, no, no! Bwut!
I'll get it!
That's it, Bingo! Eeee!
-Oh, dear child.
You grow up so fast.
Aw, Dad, let go!
Bingo, get it!
Don't let it touch the ground!
Bluey, help!
I can't do it by myself!
Dear child, embrace your father.
Let go!
Bwut!
-Aah!
-I'll get it!
Oh, this heat is oppressive.
I'll just turn on this fan.
-Dad!
Mine! Mine!
There's leaves everywhere!
Dad! Aaaah!
Ah, there's too many toys
on the ground! Bwut!
Who is responsible
for this mess?
My, my, all these toys
left lying around
sure are making it difficult
to keep the balloon up.
We know!
Can you imagine how easy
this would be
if you'd tidied them all away?
That isn't helping!
Oh, no!
-Ooh!
Ha ha! See, Dad?
Our toys saved the balloon.
Not for long!
-No!
- You get it!
-Yah!
Aah!
It's heading
for the fan!
Oh, no!
-We can't let it touch the ground!
-We know!
-Bwut!
No, I mean, we really can't
let it touch the ground.
Balloons pop
if they touch grass!
What?
You said nothing would happen!
It's my last balloon!
Catch it!
-Aah!
- Aah! Aah!
It's going
into Lucky's yard!
Lucky, the balloon!
Get it, Lucky!
Got it! Bwut!
Aah! Lucky!
I'm not gonna make it!
Oh, no!
Mine! Mine!
Yours, Lucky! Get onto it!
Good one, Dad.
I got it, I got it!
-That's it, boy!
I got it! Mine!
Oh, I've done me hammy.
You get it, Lucky.
Lucky, get it!
-Okay, Bluey!
Yah! There ya go, Bluey!
Thanks, Lucky's Dad!
No worries, Bluey.
I can catch it. I can catch it!
Catch it, Mum!
Looks like rain!
-No!
Ohh.
Aw, my balloon.
It's popped.
It's all good.
We can blow up another one.
But that was my last balloon.
Oh.
Did I make that
a little too fun?
-Yes.
-Yeah, you did.
Sorry, squirts.
It's a hard one to get right.
It was pretty fun, though.
Yeah,
it was definitely quite fun.
Yeah, it was really fun.
You know, I think we've got
one last balloon left.
- Really?
-For real life?
Yeah... a big blue one.
Uh-oh.
Blow up the Daddy balloon!
-Yeah!
Ready!
Shall we play keepy uppy?
Unh-unh!
Ohh.
What? What?
Go free, birdie!
Pbhhhhhhhht!
Oh, no!