Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
Today, Polly, the cousins
are coming over.
Mum and Aunt Trixie
are gonna play hockey.
That means we can play horsey
with Dad and Uncle Stripe.
Is that gonna be fun?
Yeah, I think so.
Ohh, good Polly Puppy.
- Bluey!
They're here!
Bluey, last time
the cousins visited,
you got upset because they
spilled passion fruit
all over Polly Puppy.
Oh, yeah,
I better put her away.
'Cause she's
your special puppy.
Yes! I'll put her in my room.
Oh, there's my watermelon!
Aah!
Nom nom nom nom!
Gidday, Bingo.
Gidday, Bluey.
Hello, Bandit.
-Hi.
Hey kids, how're ya goin'?
-Hey, brother.
-Hey.
Ooh, show Aunt Chilli
your thongs, Muffin.
Aunt Chilli,
I'm wearing thongs!
Oh, great!
Hello, Socks.
-Ooh!
Arghhhh!
Okay kids, Aunt Trix and I
are off to play hockey.
Have fun with Dad
and Uncle Stripe.
See ya, kids.
Quick,
let's get out of here.
-Bye!
See ya later!
All right, girls,
who wants
to sit on the couch
and watch cricket?!
Noooo!
-Not me!
No way.
Let's play
horsey ride!
Yeah!
-Ahhh.
Well, we gave it
a shot.
This episode of Bluey
is called Horsey Ride.
Giddyup, Sparkles!
Neigh!
Giddyup,
Gallahop!
-Neigh! Prrrrt!
-Neigh!
-Brrrr!
Come on, horsies.
Giddyup!
-Brrr!
When I do this,
it means giddyup!
-Giddyup!
-Oh! Ahh!
-Ahh! Ohh!
-Brrr!
Horsies love tiles.
Sparkles needs
more sparkles on her.
Ooh, I'll get
some glitter.
-Neigh!
-Brrrr!
Aaaah!
Polly Puppy!
Brrr!
Daaaad!
-Let go, Socks!
Hey, hey. Okay,
chill the beans, everyone.
Socks won't let go
of Polly Puppy!
Socks, let Polly go.
It's Bluey's special toy.
Let me try.
Hey there, Rocksocks,
how about we --
-Ow!
Well, I'm out of ideas.
I put all my special toys away
when my cousins come over.
You should have done that, Bluey.
Good idea, Muffin.
I was going to do that,
but then you ate me
like a watermelon,
and I got distracted.
No point playing
the blame game.
We need a solution.
Something for Socks that's
even more fun than Polly Puppy.
What about
a horsey ride?
Or two horsey rides?
What if we had a horsey wedding?
Yee!
Sparkles can marry Gallahop!
Huh?
And we could make confetti.
-What?
-And invite Socks!
-What was that?
-Yeah!
Oh, man.
-Socks!
We'd like to invite you
to the wedding
of Sparkles and Gallahop!
-Huh?
Hmm.
Bring out Sparkles!
[Mendelssohn's
"Wedding March" plays]
I'm the luckiest horse
in the world.
Horsies can't talk.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may Sparkles marry
Gallahop today.
Socks! The wedding
has started!
It's not working.
-Get them to say some things.
You may now
say some things.
Uh...
I'm not marrying him.
He stinks.
My heart is breaking.
I said, horsies can't talk!
Oh, I mean...
Let them get married!
You may now get married.
Neigh!
She said, you now get married!
You have to say "I do."
Yeah, but in horsey talk.
Brrr!
-Neighhh!
Sparkles!
No!
Come back,
Sparkles!
You have to do it properly!
Neigh! Ooh!
-Brrr! Brrrr!
Come back, Sparkles!
Marry Gallahop!
Now!
Brrr!
I want Polly back.
Prrrrt!
Where'd he go?
He's watching the cricket!
Get him!
Brrr! Brrr!
Neighhhh!
Neigh! Neigh!
Yeah!
Good one, Socks!
Aroooo!
I'd been
looking forward to this day
all my life,
and now it's ruined.
Neigh.
Prrrrt.
You may now say "I do."
Well, I guess that's why
we wear mouth guards.
Well, that sounds positive.
What have you kids
been up to?
Ah, you know, just regular
childhood games.
Uncle Stripe married Dad!
Yeah!
Oh, really?
-Arooooo!
Well, who could blame him?