[up-tempo music plays]
[music stops]
[all] Mum!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Dad!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Bingo!
[music resumes]
-[music stops]
-[all] Bluey!
[seagulls squawking,
waves crashing]
[wheels rolling]
[all] Beach!
[Bluey] This episode of Bluey
is called The Beach!
Mum! Beach!
Beach!
Aww, poor Mum.
She's all on her own.
Mum likes being by herself.
Huh.
I wonder why.
Beeeeeeach!
-Beach!
-[laughing]
Here comes a big one!
Ready? Steady!
[kids laugh]
I'm just gonna go
for a walk along the beach.
Why do you like walking by yourself?
Hmmmmm.
Not sure, actually.
I just do.
See you soon, little mermaid.
[wind gusting]
[waves crashing]
Whoa! Look at this shell!
Wow!
Can I go and show Mum?
Yeah, all right. Off you go.
Bingo and I will wait here.
Really?
Is that Mum
with the orange hat over there?
Yeah, that's her.
And I can go all that way
by myself?
Yeah. I'll keep an eye on you.
For real life?
Yeah. Just don't go in the water.
Okay.
But how will you get there
with no legs, mermaid?
Oh, yeah.
You can be King Neptune
and you give me legs!
Real!
Legs!
Shew!
[both laugh]
Actually, she's a bit far away.
But, little mermaid,
you can follow Mum's footsteps.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks, King Neptune.
Good luck!
I am the mermaid who got her legs!
But they only last a day, little mermaid.
So enjoy them!
Yoooooh!
Okay, I will.
Whoo!
[laughs]
[seagulls squawking]
Seagulls, can you please move?
A mermaid wants to get through.
Dad, can you --
Oh. That's right.
Dad's back there.
[squawking continues]
Well...
then...
-[barking]
-[squawking intensifies]
[laughs]
[gasps]
[groans]
You cheeky wave!
You washed away
my mum's footsteps!
-[chirps]
-Ooh!
Pippies!
[chirps]
Pippies coming up for wee-wees!
[laughs]
[laughing] Ohh!
Oh! Hey, mate.
Where you going, little matey?
Pinchy, pinchy!
I'm the mermaid
who got her crab legs!
Where are you going, pinchy?
Okay, see you.
Aaaaah!
[laughs]
Oh, orange speck Mum is getting bigger.
Mum!
I got a shell to show you!
Oh, she can't hear you.
Better keep going.
I'm coming!
Whoa! Jellyfish!
Ha ha!
You can't sting me, jellyfish!
I am the mermaid who got her legs!
♪ Aaaaaah
[gasps]
An old castle.
I wonder who lived here.
Maybe this is where
the other mermaids live.
-[squawks]
-[gasps]
Hello.
Um, would you mind moving?
I need to show this shell to my mum.
[squawks]
Aaaaah!
Maybe I will just head back.
I think I've had enough
walking by myself.
Oh.
Dad's just a blue speck.
Can't go backward.
Can't go forward.
What am I gonna do?!
[gasps]
Mum's footsteps!
Phew!
Little mermaid's just gotta be brave.
I am the mermaid who got her legs,
but only for a day!
[squawking]
Aaah!
[squawking continues]
Thanks for moving, Mr Pelican!
Bluey!
Mum!
[both laughing]
Did you come all this way by yourself?
Yeah!
I'm a mermaid who got her legs!
Past the jellyfish?
Yeah!
And the pelican.
And I saw a whole herd of crabs!
You little star!
Listen to this!
[gasps]
Whoo!
[squawks]
I love walking by myself.
Oh, yeah?
Why's that?
Um, I don't know.
I just do.
But this is nice, too, though.
[up-tempo music plays]