Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
What's the time,
Mrs. Wolf?
Seven o'clock!
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven!
What's the time, Mrs. Wolf?!
Ten o'clock!
Coco!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine ten!
What's the time, Mrs. Wolf?
Dinnertime! Got you!
Coco!
You always do this!
Do what?
Something to make
the game easy for you.
-Do I?
-Yes.
Oh, sorry, Bluey.
I'll try and stop.
What if we play
Shadowlands instead?
Yeah!
This episode of Bluey
is called Shadowlands.
What's Shadowlands?
It's fun.
All the shadowy, grassy bits
are the land,
and all the bits in the sun
is the sea.
Yeah, and there's crocodiles
in the sea.
Yeah,
you can't touch the water,
or you get bitten
by a crocodile.
So you can only walk
on the land?
These bits?
Yeah, and we have to getnfrom here
to the picnic blanket.
All right!
But you can't just
change the rules
to make it easy this time,
okay?
No, I won't.
You promise?
I promise.
Okay, let's go!
-Yeah!
Whoo!
This is fun!
I told you.
You won't get us, crocodile.
Ooh! I can't jump that far.
Look at my little legs.
Well, maybe just this time,
you can have
crocodile-proof shoes.
Coco!
Oh. Yeah. Sorry.
But how is Snickers
gonna get over?
Umm...
I know!
Come here, Coco!
Now get on my shoulders.
Go, Snickers!
Yeah! We did it!
Great idea, Bluey!
Hey, this bug
looks like bird poo.
[car alarm chirps,
engine starts]
Bluey, look out!
Bluey!
Aaaaah!
You're trapped.
How are you gonna
get across the river?
I don't know.
How about we just pretend
in this bit,
all the crocodiles are asleep?
You can't
change the rules, Coco!
Ohh! Why not?
Because they're the rules!
Look! A bus!
Are you ready, Bluey?
I'm ready!
Go!
Aaaaah!
Go, Bluey!
Eeee-yaaaah!
Yeah!
That was so cool!
Come on!
We're almost
at the picnic blanket!
Be careful, everyone.
This bridge is really skinny.
Wait!
-It's getting windy!
The wind's making it move!
I can't stay on!
Aaaaah!
The crocodiles
are gonna get us!
What are we gonna do?!
Run!
Phew! We made it!
But look.
There's no way
to get across the sea!
And we can't go back this way.
We're trapped
on a palm tree island!
Oh, noooo!
The little critters
must be hungry.
Oh, I brought something
for them.
Cupcakes!
Who wants cupcakes?
They've got blue icing!
And sprinkles!
Sprinkles!
Why don't we just make it
so we can...
walk on water?
No one can walk on water.
Water boatmen can.
Well, we aren't water boatmen.
We need to find another way.
I'm going to eat your cupcakes!
No!
That's it!
I'm gonna be a water boatman
and walk across this water
and have a cupcake.
No, Coco!
-Arr-oooh!
But I want a cupcake!
You can't just
change the rules!
But you still haven't
told me why!
Well, because...
I don't know!
See? There's no reason.
Maybe Coco's right, Bluey.
Maybe we can just change
the rules an eensy bit?
It'll still be Shadowlands.
Okay.
Wait!
What is it?
The wind is back.
Look!
It's blowing the cloud.
It's heading towards the sun.
Run!
Quick!
Hurry up, Snickers!
Run your little
sausage dog legs!
I can't run any faster!
Oof!
The crocodiles are coming!
Aaaaaaah!
We did it!
That was so much fun!
Yeah!
That's why you can't
change the rules--
because the rules make it fun!
Oh, yeah!
Kids and cupcakes, eh?
A cupcake for each hand,
Snickers?
You got it made in the shade.
What's the time,
Mrs. Wolf?!
Three o'clock!
One, two, three!
What's the time, Mrs. Wolf?!
Um...
Maybe this one
will be dinnertime.
It won't.
Coco always waits until
we're right up next to her
before she says--
Dinnertime!