Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
This episode of Bluey
is called Takeaway.
Ooh, can I have a shower
under that tap?
No wet dogs in car.
-Aww!
-Dad?
Yeah, mate?
Where do rocks come from?
Uhhh...
Can we have some
of your takeaway, too?
-Yeah!
-You girls don't like spicy.
Ooh, I like spicy.
You squirts wait here.
I'll be two seconds.
-Raaah!
Alright!
Let's boogie.
-Yeah!
-Yes, boogie.
Hang about!
Stay.
Aaah!
Pbbt!
Five more minutes, kids.
They forgot the spring rolls!
Hey, babe. What's up?
They forgot
the spring rolls!
Oh! Your Dad
and spring rolls!
They're just cooking 'em now.
Forget 'em, babe.
The kids must be starving.
Not...leaving...
without...spring rolls.
Say "See ya, Mum."
See ya, Mum!
-Well, good luck.
Leave without
the spring rolls?
Is she crazy?
How long is five minutes?
Uh, it's one episode
of "Chutney Chimp."
What are we
gonna play?
We're gonna play
Dad Reads The Newspaper.
Ooh, can I buy a juice?
What do these words say?
No idea, kiddo.
And no. There's a tap over there
if you're thirsty.
Please, can I have
a shower in it?
Don't even think about it.
Dad, can you help me?
Do you need a drink, too, Bingo?
No, I'm not thirsty.
Can I eat these plants?
No, mate.
- Aah! Ohh!
Which way do you turn it off?
Why are some plants food,
like lettuce,
but other plants
aren't food?
Uh, well --
Dad, can I play with these?
Uh, just two, kid.
The shop guys need 'em.
How about three?
Two.
Dad, I'm thirsty.
But I just --
Oh, never mind.
Aah!
Aww!
Quickly --grab two more,
but hang on to them.
Ohhh, I'm starving.
Can I have some takeaway?
Of course you can, customer.
Welcome to my takeaway restaurant.
Please, do sit down.
Up! Sst! Sst! Sst!
Get off!
Oh, thank you.
Here are some menus, Bingo.
You can have two,
in case you want lots of food.
My name isn't Bingo.
It's, uh...
...Tap Girl.
Can I have this, Dad?
I need to write
Tap Girl's order down.
So, Ma'am,
what would you like?
I'm just gonna check
on the spring rolls.
I'll have some
super-spicy, please.
Certainly.
I'll just get that now.
Yechh! Wet menu!
Blegh!
-Ooh!
-Me, me!
Uh, Tap Girl, I'm not sure
you can eat it for real life.
But I'm hungry.
Aah! Oh! Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Too spicy!
Ah, they're not ready yet.
Hey! My dinner!
Aaah!
Too spicy!
Okay, okay,
come here, mate.
How's that, kiddo?
Good.
But I need to do a wee.
I'm busting.
Oh, man!
Okay. Umm...
I'm a walrus.
-Excuse me --
Bluey, don't even
think about it!
Where's the nearest toilet?
Oh, that's too far!
Bingo, can you hold on till we get home?
I'm busting!
Okay, okay.
It's a bush wee.
-Dad?
-Yeah, mate?
Is everything in the whole world
made of atoms?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
Aaah!
I can't turn it off!
-Bluey!
-I only meant to turn it on a little bit!
Don't even think
about getting under that!
There's water everywhere!
Bingo, are you almost finished?
Not yet.
It's a long one.
-Get out of it!
-No, Mr Crow!
It's too spicy for you!
What will happen
if we can never turn it off?!
Get outta here!
The water will be up to the clouds!
Are you finished yet, Bingo?
Almost!
Arghhh!
This is a really long wee, Bingo!
Finished!
Get outta here!
Yeah!
Dad?
Yes, mate?
If grown-ups grow from babies
and only grown-ups have babies,
who had the first baby?
Okay, forget
the spring rolls.
Let's just get out of here.
Whoa! Ooh!
Sorry. Your spring rolls
will be five more minutes.
What?
That's a whole other
"Chutney Chimp."
Sorry about the wait.
Would you kids like
some fortune cookies?
Thank you.
What's happened out here?
They're biscuits.
With a little paper inside.
And writing on the paper.
What does it say?
It says
"Flowers may bloom again,
but a person never has
the chance to be young again."
What does that mean?
It means...
...it's shower time!
For real life?
For real life.
Spring rolls are ready!
Oh, great.
Just pop 'em on the table.
Thanks.
No worries.
Oh, that looks fun.