Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
-Ehh... easy.
Ohh! Ohh!
Bluey, easy!
- Aah! Aah!
-Oh, not fair!
-How good's Pop Up Croc?
-Again!
No. Upstairs for bedtime.
Nooooooo!
Oh, here we go.
Noooooo!
-Ooh!
This episode of Bluey
is called Fruit Bat.
All right, say goodnight to the animals.
Goodnight, frogs.
Night, kangaroos,
Night, bilbies.
Night, fruit bats.
No, not "Night, fruit bats."
They don't sleep at night.
They're octurnal.
Good knowledge, kid.
You mean fruit bats don't need
to go to bed now?
No. But you do.
Come on. Bedtime.
I wish I was a fruit bat.
Well, fruit bats don't get
to do rocket ship.
Yeah! Rocket ship!
Okay, helmets.
Choo-choog.
Seatbelts!
-Click!
Close the door.
-Clunk.
-Click.
Okay, push the button!
-Boop!
-Yeah!
Okay, shower time.
No! More rocket ship!
I don't need a shower.
Yeah, you do, ya grub.
Poahh!
Not fair!
I bet fruit bats
don't have to have showers.
Well, then they wouldn't
get to play penguins.
Yeah, penguins!
Whee!
Teeth time.
Mum, look, I'm a penguin!
Whee!
Oh, wackadu!
Even though I don't
really need to do a wee,
I'm going to do one anyway.
Otherwise, I might wet the bed.
-That's very clever, Bingo.
It's called a tactical wee.
-Not fair.
I want to stay up like a fruit bat.
Well, when the fruit bats
go to the toilet,
they do it hanging upside down,
so the wee just runs all over them.
-Blegh!
- Bleaghh!
I'd love that!
I bet you would, you little grub!
Whee! Whee!
Come on. That's a daytime game.
Oh, I just want to be a fruit bat.
Yeah, yeah. I know.
But fruit bats don't get
to play the story game,
where I tell a story,
but pretend to fall asleep.
-Yeah!
-Ah!
"So, the little puppy peeked
in the window,
and on the table was the most beautiful--"
-Wake up!
Huh? What? What? Oh, sorry.
I think I must have just dozed off.
Now, where was I?
Oh, yeah.
"...the most beautiful
golden egg she'd ever seen.
So she climbed inside,
but out jumped a huge hairy--"
-Wake up!
Aah! Aah! Spider!
Aw! I'm not tired.
I know. Just try, okay?
It's not fair!
Night, Bluey.
Ugh!
Ohh!
I can't fall asleep!
Psst! Bingo, are you awake?
Hmph!
Bluey.
What am I gonna do with you, hey?
Let me stay up?
Ehhh.
What's Dad doing?
Hmm, I'd say he's dreaming
about playing touch football
with his mates.
Really?
Yeah, he doesn't get to play
that much anymore,
so he keeps having dreams about it.
Why doesn't he get to play it
for real life?
Well, he's busy, sweetheart.
Busy working and looking after you two.
Oh.
Oh look! Did he just score a try?
I think he did.
Ooh, maybe I can dream
about being a fruit bat.
Well, you could give it a go.
Night, Mum!
Oh, okay.
Night, honey.
Come on!
Dream about being a fruit bat!
It didn't work.
Oh, well, you tried.
Where'd Dad go?
He's outside.
Dad!
Daaad!
♪ Na, na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na, na ♪
♪ La, la, la-la-la-la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la-la-la ♪
Mine!
Yes, mate, yes, mate, yes, mate!
- Kick it!
-Whoo-hoo!
Run, run!
Yeah!
Hey, Dad!
Hey, Bluey!
You're a fruit bat!
Yeah!
How is it?
It's great!
You get to eat a lot of fruit!
Ha! I bet.
Hey, did you see my try?
Yeah, I did!
How good was it?!
So good.
There's plenty more where that came from!
- Yeah, ya reckon?
-Yeah, sure.
Yeah, I do.
Oh, righto!
All right, see ya, Bluey.
Come on, let's do this!
See ya, Dad!
Wow!
Hi.
Seven o'clock!
That was a big sleep.
I had the most amazing dream.
One, two, three, four...
-Dad?
-...five, six...
Yes, mate? ...seven...
Thanks for looking after us.
...eight, nine, ten!
You're welcome.
I've got your favorite, Bluey--
fruit salad!
Yuck!
No more fruit.
Just some toast, please.
Mm-mm-mnh.