Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
You sure you don't want some help?
No.
So close!
This episode of Bluey
is called Bike.
Humph!
It's not fair!
Why can't I just
do it straightaway?
That's not how the world works, kid.
Then the world is silly!
Can't argue with that.
I'm never riding that bike again!
Okay.
Ooh.
Ooh!
Eee!
Oh. The button is unpressing.
Almost.
Ohhhh!
Oh, poor Bingo.
She'll figure it out.
Hey, look at Bentley!
I can't reach!
Oh. She can't reach the monkey bars.
Ooooh!
Aww!
Hey, look at your cousin Muffin.
Finished my water!
Put it in my backpack!
Put my backpack on my back!
One arm through.
Now the other one.
Come here, strap!
She can't get the bag on.
Oh, Muffin,
the strap's just there!
Just stick your arm through.
Look, Bingo's having another go.
Go, Bingo! Faster!
Come on, Bingo!
Come on, Bingo.
Oh!
Almost!
Oof!
That's it!
Oh, she's gonna try to jump.
Okay, here she goes.
Yay! Jumping!
Ohhhhh!
Ow!
She's okay.
Whoa!
Look at Muffin!
Waaa-aaa-aaa-aaa-aaa-aah!
Ah, don't spin 'round, Muffin!
Daddle-daddle-daddle-daddle!
Ooh!
-Ah, she's dizzy!
Ha ha!
Whoooa!
-Oh!
-Ooh!
Oh, boy.
Here comes the meltdown.
Waaaaah!
This is unacceptable!
Why won't you
go on my back, you bag?!
Whoa!
Look at Bentley!
Here she goes.
Jumping!
-Oh! So close!
-Aww!
Why can't I do it straightaway?!
Hey!
That's what I said!
Oww!
Aww.
I can't do it.
I'll never be able
to drink water again.
And then I curled
into a little ball, too.
Poor Bingo.
I'll go and hold the button for her.
Hang on.
Not so fast.
Let's just see
what happens next.
What's she doing?
Oooh!
What?!
Wait a minute.
She's got an idea!
Muffin's going for it.
Come on, Muffin!
You can do it, Muffin!
Go, Muffin!
Look at Bentley!
Go, Bentley!
Look at the focus!
She's gonna do it.
She's gonna do it!
Go, Bentley!
You can do it!
Yes!
Go, Muffin!
Yeah!
Got it!
-Yeah!
Good one, Muffin.
Yeah, good one, Muffin!
Yeah!
Almost.
Yep! Got it!
Yeah!
Go, Bentley!
Yes!
You beauty!
That was great!
I'd like to get down now.
Whoo!
How's Bingo doing?
-Oh! Bingo!
-Oh, Bingo!
That's disgusting!
That's less than ideal.
But it's still a win.
Nice work, Bingo!
Nice work, Bluey.