[up-tempo music plays]
[music stops]
[all] Mum!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Dad!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Bingo!
[music resumes]
-[music stops]
-[all] Bluey!
[birds chirping]
She came!
The Tooth Fairy came!
Hey, nice one, Bluey!
Way to go, kid.
She left me five bucks!
[sputters] Five bucks?
Yeah, I know.
Five bucks!
Five bucks?
That's what she left
all Bluey's friends.
Well, that Tooth Fairy's
doing well for herself, isn't she?
Hey, maybe you can spend it
at the markets today.
Yeah!
[Bluey] This episode of Bluey
is called Markets.
[giggling]
This little piggy
went to market,
and this little piggy stayed home.
Hey! No, I didn't.
I'm coming, too!
Check this out, Bingo.
The Tooth Fairy even put
a special sticker on here.
Wow.
What are you gonna
spend it on?
That's the question.
Hmm, that is a question.
Hmm, question.
[indistinct talking]
Bluey!
Indy!
[both laugh]
Look, Indy.
The Tooth Fairy
gave me five bucks!
Wow!
What are you gonna spend it on?
I don't know.
Can you come and help me?
Yeah!
Mum, can I go and help Bluey?
Sure thing, Indy.
I'll keep an eye on 'em.
Follow me!
Giant bubbles!
Wow!
[both laughing]
Do you wanna get one?
Yeah, I do.
Wait!
Pony ride!
Excuse me.
What's that pony's name?
Her name's Biscuits.
-Aww!
And what's that one's name?
Buttermilk.
-Aww!
[whispering] I really,
really want to ride Buttermilk.
Definitely Buttermilk.
Can we ride Buttermilk, please?
Okay, honey.
Up you get.
[straining]
Okay, Indy, you can sit in front.
Oh, I'm sorry, honey,
but you don't have enough money
for two riders.
Oh. I only want to go
if Indy can come.
It's okay, Bluey.
I'll wait here.
Hmm.
I think I've changed my mind.
Well, aren't you a good friend?
Yes, Pony Lady.
Goodbye, Buttermilk.
You're so beautiful.
[all] German sausage!
German sausage!
Okay, I want
a German sausage
and the squirty sauce,
but only on one end,
so you can have the other end.
But I'm not allowed that.
Why not?
Mum says it's got added ingredients...?
Can you have barbecue sauce?
I'm not allowed that one either.
Mustard?
I'm definitely not allowed mustard.
Well, what are we
gonna get then?
[dog] Poffertjes! Poffertjes!
Indy!
Poffertjes!
Poffertjes?
[both sniffing]
Have these got any
wheat, sugar,
gluten, or dairy
in them?
That's all they've got in them.
-Ohhh!
-Aww!
My friend can't eat them.
Bye, girls.
Poffertjes!
I just don't know what to get.
Anyone want the last toffee apple?
I've got one toffee apple left.
Oh, oh.
I will!
Lovely, jubbly.
Thank you.
I'm pretty sure that has sugar in it.
[chomping]
Ah, toffee apple.
Old school.
I'm not sure I like
this toffee apple.
Plus, Indy can't have any.
Oh, that's no good.
[singer] Thank you!
[cheers and applause]
[feedback] Ah, thanks buddy!
Aaaaaah!
That deserves a song.
[upbeat music playing]
Dad, I'm not sure
I made the right choice.
I think I want to put my
five bucks in that case
and get a song.
Oh, right.
Can I get my five bucks back?
That's not really
how it works, kiddo.
Once you've spent money, it's...
well, gone.
Oh.
Okay.
Don't worry, Bluey.
My mum always says to me,
"What goes around
comes around."
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Sweetheart, can you
go get your Dad
a German sausage, please?
Okay, Dad.
-[music stops]
-[cheers and applause]
-Here we go!
-[upbeat music playing]
[humming]
Now, that's a tune.
One sausage, please!
Thanks.
There you go.
Thanks!
Gruber, go get me a carrot juice.
Sure thing, Dad.
Carrot juice, please.
Oh, we're out of carrots.
Will you get me a bag
of carrots please, Juniper?
Yes, Mum.
I'd like these carrots, please.
Just these, please.
I'll have that one, thank you.
Indy?
Yes, Mum?
Be a sweetie.
Go and pop this in the guitar case for me.
Okay!
[gasps]
Look, Bluey!
[music stops]
Whoa!
Five bucks?
Thanks, matey!
That deserves another song.
Who likes to dance?
-Whoo-hoo!
-Ah!
2, 3, 4!
[upbeat music playing]
And this little piggy went,
-"Wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee, wee"
-[giggles]
all the way home!
Dad! I've lost
another tooth!
Ah, great.
[up-tempo music plays]