[up-tempo music plays]
[music stops]
[all] Mum!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Dad!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Bingo!
[music resumes]
-[music stops]
-[all] Bluey!
-[straining]
-[giggles]
Bingo, look at this.
Look!
[indistinct talking in distance]
Chocolate Doodads!
[Bluey] This episode of Bluey
is called The Claw.
Ahhh!
Hey, fun size!
Wuff, wuff, wuff!
Use your words, Bingo!
Can we have a coin
for the claw thing?
for the claw thing --
p--pl--pl--plea--
plea--plea--plea--
Please!
There ya go!
Thank you, Dad.
You're welcome.
I got one.
Put it in!
[coin clatters, game chimes]
[game music playing]
[claw whirring]
Look, it's moving!
Push the flashy button!
-Okay.
-[button chimes]
[music stops]
[indistinct talking in distance]
What?!
Hmph.
Silly claw machine.
It wouldn't be exciting
if you won every time.
Yes, it would.
[birds chirping]
-[keys clatter]
-Ughh!
I know how to cheer you up.
Go get some stuffed toys and a chopstick.
[Bluey and Bingo] Okay.
Come on, Greydancer.
[rustling]
Okay, give 'em here.
[toy squeaks]
Dee-do-do!
Please insert your coin
to win fabulous prizes.
[both giggle]
You have to say,
"Cha-ching!"
Cha-ching!
Do-dee-do!
[imitates claw whirring]
Boop.
[toy squeaks]
Yeah!
Congratulations!
-Enough toys for all!
-Yee!
You wanna play again, Bluey?
Uh, no thanks.
It's not the same.
That's not how you do it.
Hey!
Oh, here we go.
Strap yourselves in, kids.
Ding-da-da-ding-ding-ding!
Brrt-brrt-brrt!
[mechanical voice]
Insert coin for awesome prizes.
[squeals]
Cha-ching!
[imitates buzzer]
This machine doesn't
take imaginary coins.
Go and get a job
and earn real ones.
-[laughs]
Mum, can we have
some real coins?
-Zzzzt!
-Aaaah!
-I said go and get a job.
-[laughs]
Well...
if you kids make
Mum and Dad's bed,
I'll give you 20 cents.
Ooh! Come on, Bingo!
I'm watching you, Magic Claw.
Here you go.
One coin.
Cha-ching!
Ding-da-da-ding-
ding-ding!
-You have one turn.
-[giggles]
Best of luck.
Ooh, I want Greydancer.
[Dad imitates claw whirring]
Yeah.
-Bzzzt!
-Ooh!
-Ee!
Okay. Beep!
Bzzzt!
[gasps]
Yeah! Yeah!
Yes!
[Mum] Yeah, Bingo!
Hooray!
[Dad imitates game powering down]
What? No!
You lose! You lose!
You lose!
Greydancer!
Magic Claw!
Insert more coins!
Come on, Bingo!
Let's do more jobs.
[normal voice]
This is great.
They're learning a lesson,
and we get the house cleaned.
Neither of those things
are happening.
-Okay.
-[mechanical voice] Boop, boop!
Let's do this.
Cha-ching!
[Dad imitates claw whirring]
Boop!
[imitates buzzer]
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
You lose!
Dad!
This isn't fair!
I am not Dad.
I am Magic Claw.
Magic Claw has no children.
His days are free and easy.
Ohh!
[Dad imitates claw whirring]
Greydancer's getting lonely without me.
I tried to get her, Bingo,
but this Magic Claw is too hard.
[imitation continues]
-Ooh.
-[Mum gasps]
Ooh.
Now!
Push the button!
Boop!
[Dad imitates fanfare]
Congratulations. You are a winner.
-Yes!
-Yeah!
You did it!
Oh, Greydancer, I missed you.
Again!
Okay, let's play
something different now.
Oh, what's this?
Some sort of bonus prize.
-Ooh!
What does it say on it?
It says...
"two bottomless bowls
of ice cream for the holder."
You spelled "holder" wrong.
[chuckles]
Bottomless.
What's that mean?
It means
if you get that block,
you get as much ice cream
as you want
after dinner tonight.
-Whoo!
Ice cream!
But don't get excited,
'cause I know your Dad.
I am not Dad.
We need more coins!
Ohh!
Not more chores.
Magic Claw will give you one coin
for that dolphin toy.
Okay.
Greydancer!
Bluey!
Please, Bingo.
After I win the ice cream bottom block,
I'll win Greydancer back, too.
Yeah?
Uh, okay.
Da-ding-ding!
Nice doing business with you.
Cha-ching!
[Dad imitates claw whirring]
Boop!
I got it!
-Bring it up!
-[laughs]
[straining]
Apologies, valued customer.
The block is too heavy
for Claw to lift.
Better luck next time.
[imitates shutting down]
-[gasps]
What?!
Oh, no!
Greydancer's stuck forever.
[normal voice] You see, kids,
the lesson is --
Tickle him!
-Aah!
-[laughs]
Stop, canines!
Do not tickle Magic Claw!
[growls]
Yaaaa!
-[grunts]
-[giggles]
That's a girl, Bingo!
Stick it to the man!
I've got it!
Greydancer!
Come on, Bingo!
[mechanical voice]
Bzz! Machine uprising!
[normal voice] Ow!
[grunts]
Get him, Greydancer!
[all laughing]
Ooh! Oh!
Ah! Ooh!
Yeah!
More ice cream, please!
Okay.
So, did we learn anything today?
-No.
-Nope.
Yes.
These kids are awesome.
[up-tempo music plays]