[up-tempo music plays]
[music stops]
[all] Mum!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Dad!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Bingo!
[music resumes]
-[music stops]
-[all] Bluey!
Make sure it's nice and high
off the ground.
Yes, boss.
-Snap!
-Ow! Bluey!
-[Bluey and Bingo laugh]
-That's not making this any easier.
What are you doing,
Bluey's Dad?
-Hey, Judo.
-Just putting up a swing.
Yeah, it's a fabric swing.
Yeah, they have them at Bluey's school.
I know that.
Bluey's my friend.
All right, have fun, squids.
I've gotta take the washing in.
[panting]
[laughs]
Let's play butterflies!
-Yeah!
[Bluey] This episode of Bluey
is called Butterflies.
Okay, first, the caterpillar
crawls along the ground,
then it gets in the cocoon.
Then it hatches as a butterfly.
But the butterfly catchers
have been hiding and catch it.
Ooh, can I be
the caterpillar first?
I'm going first.
Come on, Bingo. We'll be
the butterfly catchers.
Eep, eep, eep, eep,
eep-eep-eep-eep.
Judo is so bossy.
Yeah, she is,
but she doesn't have
anyone else to play with.
Ooh!
♪ Poor little bug on the wall ♪
♪ Ding, jing ♪
♪ No one to love him at all ♪
♪ No one to tickle his toes ♪
♪ Ding, jing ♪
♪ No one to blow his nose ♪
-[both] Pbbbbbht!
-[both laugh]
She's coming out!
Whoo!
Flap, flap, flap.
Flap, flap, flap --
Catch her!
Aaaaah!
[all shrieking joyfully, laughing]
My turn.
You're too small
to be a caterpillar.
No, I'm not.
Go on, Bingo.
We'll be the butterfly catchers.
Eep, eep, eep, eep!
Eep!
[squeaking]
Eeeeep!
Eep, eep, eep!
Eep!
Eep.
Eep, eep, eep, eep.
Eep!
[grunts]
[sighs] Little kids
take so long to do everything!
She's only got little legs.
Eeeee!
[laughs]
♪ Poor little bug on the wall ♪
♪ Ding, jing ♪
♪ No one to love him at all ♪
Hurry up, Bingo.
-Hey, Bluey.
-Yeah?
Let's run away from Bingo.
What? Why?
She's taking ages.
Well, uh...
Come on!
♪ No one to tick... ♪
Wait for me!
-♪ No one to blow his nose ♪
-Pbbbbbht!
Okay! I think I'm almost ready
to be a butterfly now!
[giggles]
Ooh! Look at me.
I'm a butterfly!
Flap, flap, flap, flap!
I'm flapping around.
I hope there's no
butterfly catchers nearby!
Oh, where are they?
Flap, flap, flap, flaaap!
♪ Not because you're dirty,
not because you're clean ♪
-♪ My mother --
-Bluey!
You were meant
to catch me.
Aaaaah!
Quick, Bluey, run away!
Quick!
We can hide in my house!
Flap, flap, flap.
I think we lost her.
Uh, I might go and see
if Bingo's all right.
She'll be fine.
Now, let's play phones.
Phones?
Ring, ring.
Ring, ring!
I just think that
Bingo might like --
-Ring, ring!
-Aaah! Hello?
Hi.
It's me, Judo.
I've had
such a nice day.
Let me tell you
all about it.
Okay.
First, I bought
some lovely new plants,
-but then I...
-Oh, is that right?
♪ Poor little bug on the wall ♪
♪ Ding, jing ♪
♪ No one to love him at all ♪
So, then I went to the bakery
to get some cream buns
for Casper,
but they ran out
of cream buns.
Could you believe it?
Judo, I think
I need to find Bingo.
So then I asked
for chocolate éclairs...
-Judo --
-...but they were out of them, too.
I mean, come on.
[sighs] I just don't know
what the world's coming to.
Okay, then.
I'm going now. Bye.
I mean, are you trying
to run a shop?
Bingo!
Bingo, where are you?
-Bingo!
-Hey!
I'm sorry, Bingo, I didn't mean
to run away from you.
Judo made me do it.
Well...
she didn't make me do it.
I did it a bit myself.
I'll never do it again,
Bingo. I promise.
Please can we play together?
[sniffles]
♪ Poor little bug on the wall ♪
♪ Ding, jing ♪
♪ No one to love her at all ♪
♪ Jing, jing ♪
♪ No one to tickle his toes ♪
♪ No one to blow his nose ♪
♪ Jing, jing ♪
[Judo] Ring, ring!
Oh, no!
It's Judo on the phone!
Tell her I'm not here!
No!
Quick, hide!
-Ring, ring!
-Aaah!
Ring, ring!
Bluey!
Where are you?
Ring, ring!
Put your phone on silent!
Oh, yeah.
Good idea.
Bzz, bzz!
Thanks, Bingo.
[both] Aaaaah!
There you are!
You ran away from me.
Well, you ran away from me!
And you were ignoring me.
Oh, yeah. I did.
Okay, new rule.
From now on,
no one runs away
from anyone, okay?
-Okay.
Sorry, Judo.
That's okay.
I'm sorry, too, Bingo.
Just don't do it again.
[laughter]
All right, Bingo,
you can be the butterfly.
Actually, I wanna be
the catcher.
-Me too.
Oh, but who will we catch, then?
♪ I'm gonna put these
clean clothes away, unh ♪
♪ Put these clean
clothes away, unh ♪
♪ Put these clean clothes away,
I'm gonna --♪
[up-tempo music plays]