[up-tempo music plays]
[music stops]
[all] Mum!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Dad!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Bingo!
[music resumes]
-[music stops]
-[all] Bluey!
[both giggle]
Can you play games with us?
No time for games, squirt.
I'm working from home today.
One sec. I just
gotta pop downstairs.
Doot!
-[elevator music plays]
-[both giggle]
-[music stops]
-Okay, I'm back.
Is this yours?
Dad, play the elevator game!
I told you, kid --
no time for elevator game.
It's a work day today.
Doot!
-[elevator music plays]
-[both giggle]
-[music stops]
-I found another one!
[both laugh]
-Again!
Sorry, kids.
I got loads of work on.
Doot!
-[elevator music plays]
-I just can't play the elevator game.
[both] You are playing it!
[giggles]
[Bingo] This episode of Bluey
is called Yoga Ball.
[keyboard clacking]
[giggles]
[printer whirs]
Now, Bingo!
[both giggle]
Ugh!
Hey!
[kids giggling]
Don't even think about it!
-[both giggle]
-Stay! Stay!
Push!
You little rats!
[both giggle]
Why do you sit
on a giant green ball?
'Cause I wrecked my back
changing your nappies.
-Boing, boing, boing, boing, boing!
-[laughing]
I want a turn doing that.
[giggles]
Boing, boing...
[echoing] boing, boing, boing, boing...
[normal] boing!
Okay, now beat it.
I've gotta get to work.
Oooooooh.
No, not yet!
[kids giggle]
Bluey!
Ohh!
So, then Mixed Up Murphy says,
"Would smoothie banana you like?"
[giggles]
Oh, Ball-E, you need to sleep.
You must be so tired.
That big Dad has been
sitting on you all day.
Uh, Ball-E, which tattoo should I get?
Do you like the unicorn
or...
or the rainbow?
[deep voice]
Well, Bingo --
My name is Larn.
Well, Larn, I really think
you should get the --
-There it is!
-[both scream]
[giggling]
Out.
Can we play Delivery Chair?
No!
Oh, pleeease!
Oh, don't use
your "please" face!
Oh, all right.
Yeah, Bingo!
Delivery Chair!
That "please" face gets me every time.
Now I need to get
these two packages delivered.
But first, I need to stamp them.
Stamp!
Ooooooh.
Okay, now I need
to deliver these to --
Hmm. Let's see.
Oh, Mogadishu.
Okay, here's one package.
-[laughs]
-Oh --marked "fragile." Okay.
Well, I'd better be careful, then!
[giggles]
And here's the second package!
Ooof!
Okay, delivery over.
Now I've gotta get back to work.
Oh, come on! One more!
No!
Oooooh.
♪ Ba ba-da ba
bum bum bum ♪
Can we just quickly play that game
where we run down the hall
and you sing
♪ "Da-na-na-na"
and you roll the ball down the hall
and we jump out of the way?
Oh, you mean Raiders?
Yeah, Raiders!
-Yeah, Raiders.
-All right.
Maybe a quick game.
Hooray!
Not quick, though.
I want you to play
for...this long.
Okay.
Fair enough.
-Hooray!
-[both giggle]
-You ready?
-Yeah!
Okay...
go!
[both laughing, squealing]
Again!
Ooh!
Ooooooh.
Okay, game over.
I have to do some work.
Walk it off, sport.
Hey, Bingo.
Oh, what's the matter?
Daddy's playing too rough with me.
Yeah. He does play too rough
sometimes, doesn't he?
Yes.
Did you use your big-girl bark?
No.
Because I don't have
a very good big-girl bark.
Really? Show me.
Ruff.
Oh, that's all right.
Just do it bigger.
Ruff!
Bigger.
-Ruff!!
-Whoa!
There it is!
Come on.
Let's go talk to your Dad.
Ruff!
[keyboard clacking]
[knock on door]
Go away!
What's up?
You're in trouble!
No one's in trouble.
Bingo just has something
she'd like to tell Dad.
That's all.
Sometimes, you play
a bit too rough with me.
Aw, Bingo.
Really?
Aw, sorry, Buster.
I didn't realize.
I think I just forget
that you're a bit younger
than your sister.
I'm only 4.
Yeah, not 6, like me.
But, Dad, we don't want you
to stop playing with us.
Oh, okay.
I'm just gonna get better
at using my big-girl bark.
Okay.
Well, let's practice.
So, tell me, is this rough okay?
Boing!
[giggling]
Yes, that's okay.
Okay, how about this rough?
Boing!
[laughing] Yes, that's okay.
Okay, what about this?
-Boing!
-Ruff!
Okay. Too rough.
Now I know.
[giggles]
All right, now, clear out, you lot.
I've got to --
Hey! Where's my ball?!
[Bluey deep voice]
I'll just be a second!
[toilet flushes]
Oh, my! How rude!
Can't you see that I'm on the toilet?
[giggles]
[up-tempo music plays]