[up-tempo music plays]
[music stops]
[all] Mum!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Dad!
[music resumes]
[music stops]
[all] Bingo!
[music resumes]
-[music stops]
-[all] Bluey!
Brrrrmmmm!
Brrrmmm!
Beep, beep!
Anyone need a taxi?
[Dad] Taxi!
Taxi!
Ooh! A customer.
[panting]
I'm in a big hurry, taxi driver.
I need to get to the airport.
Hop in. I can take you to the airport.
Thanks.
I'm late for my flight to Tasmania.
Yes, sir!
Um, can I just check --
you won't break down or get lost
or pick up another passenger, will you?
Of course not.
Oh, good. 'Cause I --
Taxi!
Oh! Another passenger!
Whoa!
Ohh! I knew it!
[Bluey] This episode of Bluey
is called Taxi.
Can I put that stroller
in the boot for you?
Please do.
What's going on?
Be with you in a moment, sir!
Feel free to get out
and have a stretch.
I haven't got time for this!
Watch out, sir.
Watch out.
I am a rich lady.
Oh, gee! Gosh!
Hmph!
Where to, madam?
Click!
I'm taking Millicent
to Stumblytastics.
You got it.
Brrrmmm!
Hang on!
I thought we were going
to the airport first.
Millicent will not be late!
Okay.
It's fine.
It's probably on the way.
Let's ask SatNav.
Oh, here we go.
Beep!
SatNav, take us to Stumblytastics, please.
[Mum Monotone] Okay.
Calculating shortest route
to Stumblytastics.
Mm-hmm.
Continue on this road
for 500 meters.
Thanks, SatNav.
SatNav will get us there
in a jiffy.
Well, I should hope so!
Beep beep!
Brrrrrrm!
Oh, no!
Millicent is getting carsick.
Don't let her vomit on my seats!
[Mum] In 5 meters,
turn left onto...
this road.
-Okay!
-I think.
-Turning leeeeeft!
-[passengers] Whoaaa! Whoaaa!
[Mum] Or was it right?
I think it was right.
I'm not quite sure.
[all] Whoaaaa!
Let's just see
where this takes us.
Cheese and crackers!
We're completely lost!
Almost there, Millicent.
Oh! Wait! I recognize
that kebab shop.
Turn left here!
-Turn here!
-Okay!
-Yowwww!
-Whoaaa!
[Mum] Oh, no.
This isn't right.
Oh! Come on!
Sorry.
[giggles]
Oh, SatNav!
Waaa! Me sick!
Quick!
Get on this roundabout!
Okay!
[all screaming]
[Mum] Actually, there is a really good
dress shop around here!
SatNav, focus!
Oh, yes. Sorry!
-[screaming continues]
-Turn left here!
[all] Yaaaa!
Now...
stop!
[imitates brakes squealing]
[all] Agh!
-Blaaah!
- Aaah!
-This baby is vomiting all over me!
-Blagh! Bluh-luh-luh-luh!
Her name is Millicent!
You have arrived at Stumblytastics.
To the best of my knowledge.
Finally!
This isn't Stumblytastics.
Yeah, this is the zoo.
Beans on toast!
Why did you take us to the zoo?
I... really wanted...
to see... the penguins.
[giggles] Oh, SatNav.
I want to see the penguins, too.
Okay, let's go.
I'll get your stroller.
Unclick.
Other passenger,
feel free to have a stretch!
I don't want to have a stretch!
Please!
Can't you just take me
to the airport?
I'm late for my flight!
Sure.
Oh! Okay, let's go.
We can just make it.
Click!
I'll just turn the key.
Ning-ning-ning-
ning-ning!
Ning-a-ning-ning!
Oh, dear!
-What is it?
-Car won't start.
Oh!
Goodness gravy!
Not to worry.
I'll call the mechanic.
Beeda-beeda-boop.
It's ringing.
Hello, mechanic?
[Bingo] Hello, love!
What's your problem?
We've broken down!
I'll be right there, love.
Boop!
She'll be right here.
Oh, good.
I'm right here!
Hi.
Open your bonnet, please.
Pop!
Unclick.
Hmm.
Oh, yeah, love.
It's your doodad.
Oh, the doodad.
Yeah, love. You need a new doodad.
Okay, a new doodad.
It's this doodad.
Oh, right. A new doodad.
Yeah, love.
Will this take much longer?!
Fix, fix, fix.
There ya go, love.
Bye!
Thanks!
-Phew!
-Click!
I think I can just
make my flight, if we hurry.
Okay, let's go!
Brrrm!
-[imitates brakes squealing]
-Aah!
What is it now?!
Why have we stopped?!
[old woman's voice]
We need to get
some sausages,
love.
[old woman's voice]
How many do we need?
Oh,
I don't know.
Oh! Hurry up,
you old chooks!
Arghh!
Old people.
Let's go!
Okay!
Ning-ning-ning-
ning-ning-ning!
Ning-a-ning-a-ning!
Oh, what now?!
Oh, sorry about this,
but we're out of petrol.
Arghhh!
That's it!
I'm going on foot!
Good day to you! Slam!
[panting]
Have a nice evening!
Where is that airport?
Must be around here somewhere!
[breathlessly]
Oh! Hello!
Is this the airport?
Yes. You've just made it.
Boarding pass?
Oh.
Yes, of course.
[sniffs]
What's that smell?
Baby vomit.
Oh. Well, the plane
is just through here.
You have seat 4F,
just to your left.
Have a nice flight.
4D...4E...
4F! Here we go.
What a day!
Millicent, I do hope
you don't get airsick, too.
Hello!
Arghh!
Don't take off!
I want to get off!
Where's the pilot?!
I demand to speak to the pilot!
Yoo-hoo!
That's me!
I'm the pilot!
Ohhh, biscuits!
[up-tempo music plays]