Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
All right, kids, time to tidy up.
-Ohh, Mum!
We don't like tidying.
There's no way around it, I'm afraid.
-Ohhh!
Hey, Bingo, let's get
Daddy Robot to do it.
Yeah!
This episode of Bluey
is called Daddy Robot.
Hey, Daddy Robot!
Oh, uh...
Yes, Master. Brrt brrp.
We need you to do something.
Come with us to the playroom.
Brrt brrp. Yes, Master.
-Zzzt! Zzzt! Zzzt...
-Wait.
Actually, carry us to the playroom.
Yes, Master.
Anh! Ooh! Anh! Ooh!
We have to robo-boogie there.
Brrp! Yes, Master.
Daddy Robot, we order you
to tidy up the playroom.
Brrt brrp! To serve my masters
is the highest honor.
It's working!
Ahh!
Ahh! So relaxing.
Yeah, this is how we should always do it.
Yeah.
Actually, Daddy Robot,
we never want to tidy
the playroom ever again.
Yeah, ever again.
Never again?
Never again.
Ever. At all.
You understand?
Yes, Master. Brrrt boop boop.
Recalculating objectives.
Brrrt boop boop boop.
Aah! What are you doing,
Daddy Robot?
Following Master's orders. Brrrt brrrp.
Aah! Put us down!
I love Daddy Robot.
Where are you taking us?!
Brrrp. To the wheelie bin.
What?! Why?!
You two are the reason
playroom is always untidy.
If I throw you in wheelie bin,
playroom will always be tidy,
and then you will never have to
tidy playroom ever again.
-What?!
It's a solid plan, Master.
Mum!
Daddy Robot is gonna
throw us in the wheelie bin!
Oh, no!
Quick, Mum, we need the sprayer!
-Catch!
-Brrrt brrrp boop.
Ooh-ahh-eee-eee-ahh-ooh! Brrrrr!
Syntax error! Zz zz!
Please press "Play" on tape. Brrt brrt.
He's malfunctioning!
Bee brrrp eee!
Why was Daddy Robot
throwing you in the wheelie bin?
Oh. Um, well...
Must tidy up. Bee brrp brrp.
Come here, vacuum cleaner.
Aah!
-I'm not a vacuum cleaner!
Yeah, Daddy Robot,
she's not a vacuum cleaner.
Oh, yes. Brrt brrt. My mistake.
This is not a vacuum cleaner.
I told you!
-It's a banjo!
-What?!
Hey, that's my sister, not a banjo!
Brrt brrp. What are you doing
out of the laundry basket?
Laundry basket?!
Yes. You are laundry.
I folded you this morning.
-Come here.
-Aaaaaaah!
Fold, fold, fold, fold, fold!
I'm not laundry!
She's not laundry!
Oh, no. A Guinea pig has escaped.
What?!
Aah!
Mum! Daddy Robot thinks I'm a guinea pig!
What should I do?!
Ya! Ya! Ya! Ya!
Come back here, guinea pig.
You have to push his nose to turn him off!
But how?
I know! I've got an idea!
Brrbraa! Brrbraa! Brrbaa!
La la!
Look, Daddy Robot.
Bzzt!
It's a Mummy Robot.
Brrrrt! Hello.
Cheese and crackers.
You're the most beautiful robot
I've ever seen.
Boop boop boop! You are too kind.
My name is Daddy Robo--
-Da-da-da-da-da-da-da! Brrrp.
That was a little odd.
Please pretend I didn't just do that.
It is hard to unsee something like that.
Even so...
-Aah!
Off me, you furry creatures!
All right, now! Turn him off!
Touch his nose! Touch his nose!
Beep!
Powering down...
Cursed to depart,
having only just known your beauty.
Ohh!
Poor Daddy Robot.
Screwdriver.
-Please fix him.
- I'll try my best.
These circuits are badly damaged.
-Aww.
-Ha!
It's strange, though.
Daddy Robots don't usually
go crazy like that.
Well, actually, it's our fault.
We ordered Daddy Robot
to tidy the playroom for us.
And that's when he tried to
throw you in the wheelie bin?
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
Okay. I'll tell you a secret.
Daddy Robots will always find
the easiest way to do a job.
-Oh!
Just... like...
-kids!
I hope he's okay.
Boooeeee!
Hello, Daddy Robot.
How are you feeling?
Doo-doo-doo-doo- doo-doo!
I dreamt I met a robot angel.
Zzt!
Hello, Master. What are my orders?
Brrrp!
Follow us.
Bip bip bip bip brrt brrp.
Now sit down.
Zzt! Yes, Master?
Now lie back.
Zzt! Are you sure, Master?
Zzt! Shouldn't I tidy
something up for you?
-No.
We order you to relax, Daddy Robot.
Bzzt! Zzt! Zzzt!
-Zzzt! Zzzt!
I've never relaxed before.
Is this right?
Usually, you close your eyes.
Brrr...
brrrt!
Look who's here!
Brrrt! Hello again.
Boop boop rrrrrr!
Cheese and crackers.
Beeboop boop boop boop. Zzzt! Zzzt.
You robots relax.
We're gonna tidy the playroom.
Come on, Bingo.
-Bye, robots!
This... feels like... a robo-dream.
Well, kiss me before you wake up.
-Oooh!